Guide to the Yale University Art, Architecture, and Art History Theses and Projects
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Master of Environmental Design theses, 2016-2018; Accession 2019-A-0037
  - Yin, Shuyi "Preservation at War: Cultural Heritage and Its Media", 2018 (Box 1, Folder 5)